Guide to the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Records, 1750-2014 and undated RL.10159
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina records
1750-2014 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina
Rogoff, Leonard
RL.10159
34.1 Linear Feet
42.6 Gigabytes
The Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina records span the years 1750 to 2014 and document the origins and daily operations of the organization, which preserves and presents the history of the Jewish people of North Carolina through public programming, exhibits, and other projects. The collection includes documents and digital material related to the planning, funding, and carrying out of various exhibits, events and projects, especially the multimedia program "Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina." Also present are primary and secondary research materials collected by JHFNC historian Leonard Rogoff related to the history and culture of Jews in North Carolina and southern Jewish identity. Types of materials in the collection include financial statements, meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, typescripts, newsletters, marketing materials, photographs, research notes, and audiovisual material. Digital materials include photographs, administrative and promotional materials, and project design materials.
Provenance
The Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in June, 2014.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Original audiovisual materials may require production of listening or viewing copies before use.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Historical note
The Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina (JHFNC) is an independent organization dedicated to preserving and presenting the history of the Jewish people of North Carolina. Through public programming and exhibits, the JHFNC aspires to educate and showcase the richness of Jewish Life as well as promote a familiarity with the culture and lifestyle of Jews to the general public.
Chronology
1992 The organization begins as the Efraim and Marian Rosenzweig Judaica and Hebraica Exhibit at the Judea Reform Congregation, with the original Rosenzweig collection of art, artifacts, and rare books relating to Jewish Family life.
1995 The Rosenzweig Museum is established, with the goal of displaying a collection of Judaica bequeathed to Durham's Judea Reform Congregation.
1996 The museum is incorporated as an independent non-profit organization and renamed The Rosenzweig Museum of the Jewish Family (also known as The Museum of the Jewish Family and Rosenzweig Gallery), with Lenora Ucko as Director.
1999 The organization's name is changed to the Rosenzweig Museum and Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina.
2003 The Rosenzweig Museum and the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina divide into two entities.
Collection Overview
The Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina (JHFNC) records span the years 1750 to 2014 and document the origins and daily operations of the organization. The collection includes documents and digital material related to the planning, funding, and carrying out of various exhibits, events and projects, especially the multimedia program "Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina." Also present are primary and secondary research materials collected by JHFNC historian Leonard Rogoff related to the history and culture of Jews in North Carolina and southern Jewish identity.
Types of materials in the collection include financial statements, meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, typescripts, newsletters, marketing materials, photographs, research notes, and audiovisual material. Digital materials include photographs, administrative and promotional materials, and project design materials.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into four series: Administrative records, Exhibits, events and projects, Subject files, and Audiovisual.
Related Materials
Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina collection of Jewish historical materials, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina oral history collection, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina graphic arts collection, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
North Carolina temple and synagogue historical collection, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Aaron Michael Barker papers, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Bloom Store daybooks and ledger, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Samet family papers, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Stern family papers, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Joseph Leo Blumenstein papers, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Jewish art -- United States -- Exhibitions; Jewish families -- North Carolina; Jews -- North Carolina -- History; Jews -- North Carolina -- Social life and customs; Jews -- United States -- Identity; Judaism -- History; Museums -- North Carolina -- Durham; Nonprofit organizations -- North Carolina -- Durham; Rabbis -- North Carolina; Synagogues -- North Carolina; Audiovisual materials; Documentaries (motion picture genre); Photographs
- Administrative records, 1922-2014 and undated; 1; 3.3 Linear Feet; 5.3 Gigabytes
  Scope and Contents
  The materials in this series document the daily operations of the JHFNC and its predecessor organizations, beginning with the Efraim and Marian Rosenzweig Judaica and Hebraica Exhibit at the Judea Reform Congregation. The series also contains materials related to the building of the foundation's archival collections and documents the ultimate destination of archival materials and museum artifacts after the 2003 separation of the JHFNC and Rosenzweig Museum.
  Types of material in the series include financial statements, board and committee meeting agendas and minutes, correspondence, reports, bylaws, articles of incorporation, newsletters, artifact appraisals, accession worksheets, loan and donor agreements, photographs of objects, and background research on specific artifacts. Digital materials in the series include computer and email backups, donor and contact databases, marketing and promotional materials, and digital photographs and documents related to museum accessions.
  Throughout the series, titles of folders related to specific Rosenzweig/JHFNC accessions reflect the 6-digit accession numbering system established by the Rosenzweig Gallery, with the first two digits representing the year the artifact or archival material was accessioned.
  Arrangement
  The folders are arranged chronologically and alphabetically thereafter.
  - Donora, PA, congregation, 1922, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anglo-Jewish silver, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ketubah and amulets, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Books, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chanukah lamps, 1977, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - MJF, 1980, 1989, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Untranslated Buber essay, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Misc. topics, background, 1985, 1988 and undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beth El Synagogue exhibit at Duke: Jewish Ceremonial Art, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Accession 89.24.01], 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rosenzweig Museum correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [Accessions 91.01.01-91.03.01], 1991; 1 of 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [Accessions 91.01.01-91.03.01], 1991; 2 of 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - [Accessions 91.01.01-91.03.01], 1991; 3 of 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - [Accessions 91.01.01-91.03.01], 1991; 4 of 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - [Accessions 91.01.01-91.03.01], 1991; 5 of 6 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - [Accessions 91.01.01-91.03.01], 1991; 6 of 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Acquisition confirmation, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Rosenzweig acquisitions and loans - digital material, 1991-1995, 2004, 2007 and undated; 43 files Files; 398.1 Megabytes
    These digital files include photographs of museum artifacts and text documents related to Rosenzweig acquisition and conservation policies.
  - [Accessions 92.01.01-92.06.01], 1992; 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - [Accessions 92.01.01-92.06.01], 1992; 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fabric - textiles, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Appraisal Info Notes, 1992, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Reference - Misc., 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [Accessions 93.01.01-93.22.04], 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Conservation, 1993, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Items on Loan to NC Museum of History, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - [Accessions 94.10.01-94.30.01], 1994; 1 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - [Accessions 94.10.01-94.30.01], 1994; 2 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - [Accessions 94.10.01-94.30.01], 1994; 3 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - [Accessions 94.10.01-94.30.01], 1994; 4 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Hanging Sabbath Lamps [91.01.10], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Mizrach (East), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - [Other Jewish Museums]: Israel Museum Info, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Spice boxes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Torah Wrapper - Wimpel, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Rosenzweig Collection - Folk Art and New Additions, 1994, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Books, 1994-1995 and undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - [Incoming Loan and Donor Agreement - The Rosenzweig Museum and JHFNC], 1994-2010; 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - [Incoming Loan and Donor Agreement - The Rosenzweig Museum and JHFNC], 1994-2010; 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - [Accessions 95.08.01-95.41.01], 1995; 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - [Accessions 95.08.01-95.41.01], 1995; 2 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Accessions 95.08.01-95.41.01], 1995; 3 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Appraisals, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cataloging Work Done by Samantha Baskind, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Judea Reform Today Bulletins, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Survival in Sarajevo - Duke Exhibit, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Museum History, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [Accessions 96.08.01-96.43.01], 1996; 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - [Accessions 96.08.01-96.43.01], 1996; 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Appraisal Workbook, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - [Donation], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hanukkah Postage Stamps, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Megan, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mozambique, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Museum of the Jewish Family - Directors Proposal, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Museum of the Jewish Family - Fundraising, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [Other Jewish Museums]: Misc. Jewish Museums, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - [Photographs - Rosenzweig Museum - Cleaning Walls], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Registrar Workbook, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - [Rosenzweig Judaica and Hebraic Museum Judea Reform Congregational Temple Fair Market Value Appraisal], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Beth El Bulletins, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Museum of the Jewish Family Reorganization - Publicity, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - [Newsletters and Correspondence - Museum of the Jewish Family and Rosenzweig Gallery], 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - MJF Minutes, 1996-2002; 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - MJF Minutes, 1996-2002; 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - [Accessions 97.03.01-97.53.01], 1997; 1 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - [Accessions 97.03.01-97.53.01], 1997; 2 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - [Accessions 97.03.01-97.53.01], 1997; 3 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - [Bill of Sale of Agreement between the Judea Reform Congregation and The Museum of the Jewish Family and Rosenzweig Gallery], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Finances - Judea Reform Congreg Contribution - Budget, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Women in Upper Midwest, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Museum of the Jewish Family - Sundays at the Rosenzweig Gallery, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Museum of the Jewish Family - Tax Exempt, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - [Other Jewish Museums]: Nat'l Museum of American Jewish Military History, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - [Other Jewish Museums]: Temple Emanuel NYC, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Rosenzweig Gallery, 1997, 2005 and undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - MJF Publicity/Fundraising, 1997-1998, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - [Bulletin - Museum Horizons], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - [Accessions 98.01.01-98.64.01], 1998; 1 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [Accessions 98.01.01-98.64.01], 1998; 2 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - [Accessions 98.01.01-98.64.01], 1998; 3 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - [Accessions 98.01.01-98.64.01], 1998; 4 of 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Amulets, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stephen Smith's Scrapbook, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Temporary Loan - Boisson, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - MJF Board/Bylaws/Mission, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - [Accession 99.01.01], 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - [Rosenzweig Museum and Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Board Meetings], 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - JHFNC website - digital material, 2000-2001, 2004-2006, 2015 and ongoing; 875 Files; 59.9 Megabytes
    These digital files include backup copies of HTML and image files related to the JHFNC website through 2006. Also included are annual website captures beginning in 2015.
  - Rosenzweig Museum Minutes, 2000-2001, 2005, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - JHFNC Minutes, 2001-2007; 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - JHFNC Minutes, 2001-2007; 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - [JHFNC Non-Profit Status], 2001-2010 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - [Accession 2002.02.01] (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - [Draft - Bylaws of the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina], 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - JHFNC Meeting, 2002, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - [JHFNC Reconciliation Summaries], 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - JHFNC/Rosenzweig donor and contact databases, 2002-2010; 1947 Files; 175.6 Megabytes
    These digital files include Microsoft Access database files and Excel spreadsheets containing JHFNC mailing lists and donor information as well as data on Rosenzweig Museum artifacts.
  - JHFNC digital backups and archives, 2003-2006 and undated; 2822 files Files; 2.13 Gigabytes
    These digital files were created as backups of administrative material related to the JFHNC, the Rosenzweig Gallery, and various JHFNC projects. Materials include documents and images used for annual appeals ("Case for support"), publicity mailings and posters, letterhead and business cards, donation and pledge acknowledgement letters, and information about the JHFNC board. Files related to the Down Home project include images, design files, internal memos, budgets, project schedules and updates, and information for local campaigns in Greensboro, Wilmington, Durham/Chapel Hill, and Charlotte.
  - [Rosenzweig Museum Artifacts], 2004 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - [A Year of Accomplishment: The JHFNC in 2005] (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - [JHFNC Board Meeting Minutes], 2005 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - [JHFNC Reconciliation Summaries], 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - [JHFNC Newsletters], 2005-2010 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - JHFNC Board Meeting, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - [JHFNC Board Meeting Minutes and Financials], 2006 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - JHFNC/Rosenzweig Museum email backup, 2006; 169 Files; 85.8 Megabytes
    These digital files include backup copies of emails dating from September 2004 to November 2005.
  - JHFNC - digital promotional material, 2006-2009; 220 Files; 2.49 Gigabytes
    These digital files consist of documents and images related to 2009 marketing campaign conducted through Square One, as well as other files related to JHFNC promotional efforts such as the Down Home campaign. Types of material include strategy and planning documents, design files, business cards, and newsletters.
  - [JHFNC Board Meeting and Staff], 2006, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - [JHFNC], 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - JHFNC Board Meeting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - [JHFNC Board Meeting and Election of Officers], 2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - JHFNC Board Meeting Minutes, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - [JHFNC Development Strategy], 2008 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - [Letter of determination from the IRS], 2008 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - JHFNC Annual Board Meeting and Election of Officers, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - JHFNC Board Meeting, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - [JHFNC Bylaws - unsigned], 2010 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - [JHFNC Board Meetings], 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - JHFNC Financial Statements, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - JHFNC Strategic Planning Meeting, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Jewish Studies Colloquium at Duke University, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - JHFNC April Board Meeting, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - [JHFNC Meetings], 2011 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - JHFNC Website, 2011; 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - JHFNC Website, 2011; 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - [JHFNC Meeting minutes], 2011-2013 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - JHFNC Board Meeting, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - [Bill of Sale and Agreement between JHFNC and Judea Reform Congregation], 2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Beer Stein, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chanukah Info, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Coin of Judah, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gimesh: Stein's Antiques Fayetteville, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - [JHFNC Board of Directors], undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - [JHFNC Brochures], undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - JHFNC Marketing - Square One, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Museum of the Jewish Family - Office Chapel Hill Street, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Other non-Western cultures, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Photos of Torah Binder, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - [Photographs - Museum of the Jewish Family and Rosenzweig Museum artifacts], undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Sketches of Museum Items, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Southern Historical Collection, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Laptop computer hard drive (Box 40)
    Sony VAIO laptop computer. Disk image has been created from the laptop's hard drive, but is otherwise unprocessed.
    Conditions Governing Access
    The contents of the laptop have not been appraised and are closed pending appraisal and processing.
- Exhibits, events, and projects, 1908-2012 and undated; 2; 9.7 Linear Feet; 36.8 Gigabytes
  This series contains materials related to the several exhibits, events, and projects that the Rosenzweig Gallery and JHFNC initiated, funded, and organized in Durham, NC, and elsewhere. Major projects and exhibits represented include "What We Brought with Us," "Migrations," Rosenzweig Gallery art exhibits and annual juried art shows, "A History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC," and "Down Home."
  The materials in this series are arranged into two subseries: Down Home and Other exhibits, events and projects.
  Related Materials
  Oral history recordings and transcripts related to Down Home, Migrations, and other projects are located in the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Oral History Collection. Other audiovisual material related to Rosenzweig/JHFNC projects is located in the Audiovisual Series.
  - Down Home, 1995-2012 and undated; 1
    The materials in this subseries document the multimedia program "Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina" from its inception to its execution. The materials related to the exhibit include correspondence, concept plans, various design drafts and revisions, meeting notes, exhibit plans, outlines, docent notes, artifacts lists, and scripts and curricula associated with the exhibit. Materials related to the Down Home film and book includes contracts, drafts and revisions, correspondence, talks and events, and promotional materials. The subseries also contains materials related to the JHFNC's fundraising and marketing efforts for the Down Home project, including events, mailing campaigns, prospectuses, and various grant applications.
    Digital materials in this series consist of digitized photographs, historical documents, and design files used in the research for Down Home and the creation of the exhibit, book, documentary film, promotional materials, and related products. Also included are digital photographs of events related to Down Home.
    The materials in this subseries are arranged chronologically.
    - Correspondence, 1995, 2000, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Bills/Invoices [Photo Reproductions], 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Permission Forms, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition Module, 1998-2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Film - Resources, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Down Home exhibit text - digital material, 1999, 2003; 11 Files; 0.8 Megabytes
      These digital files consist of text documents related to Down Home exhibit panels.
    - Down Home- digital administrative material, 1999-2006; 1003 Files; 377.1 Megabytes
      These digital files include documents and images related to Down Home planning, including budgets, meeting notes, strategy and publicity material, and grant applications. Additional files related to the planning, organization, and funding of the Down Home project can be found in the Administrative series, JHFNC digital backups and archives.
    - Website - Database documentation, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Down Home research - digitized photographs, historical documents, and other digital material, 2000-2010; 2688 Files; 17.4 Gigabytes
      These digital files include photographs of and historical documents related to the various municipalities, businesses, temples, synagogues, community centers, families, and individuals profiled in Down Home. Many of the images were used previously in the Migrations exhibit, as is reflected by folder names and creation dates within the file directories. Some of the images originated from the special collections and archives of other institutions, usually indicated by disc label or folder names.
    - Asheville - Down Home, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - DH - Charlotte, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Greensboro Fundraising, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - NCMH/Dept Cul Res, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Down Home Budget, 2001-2007 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - DH Meetings, 2001-2009 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - NC Jewish Lists, 2001-2009 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - DH - NEH, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - [Down Home Fundraising], 2002 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Grant - Great Greensboro Comm Fdn, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Grant - Z.Smith Reynolds, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - NC MH, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Wilmington - Cape Fear Museum, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Greensboro Comm. Fdn., 2002, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - DH Advisory Board, 2002, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Prospects U-Z, 2002, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - [Down Home], 2002-2003, 2009, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - ZSRF Application, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Prospects A-E, 2002-2006; 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Prospects A-E, 2002-2006; 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - DH Film Script, 2002-2007; 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - DH Film Script, 2002-2007; 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - [Down Home fundraising], 2002-2008 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Donors for Down Home, 2002-2010; 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Donors for Down Home, 2002-2010; 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)